The true story of how Bill Gates and Steve Jobs changed the world.
Pirates of Silicon Valley is a drama, tv movie film directed by Martyn Burke.
The story about the men who made the world of technology what it is today, their struggles during college, the founding of their
companies, and the ingenious actions they took to build up the global corporate empires of Apple Computer Inc.
and Microsoft Corporation.
Steve Jobs, played by Noah Wyle.
Bill Gates, played by Anthony Michael Hall.
Steve Wozniak, played by Joey Slotnick.
Ridley Scott, played by J.G. Hertzler.
Captain Crunch, played by Wayne Pére.
Mrs. Wozniak, played by Sheila Shaw.
Pirates of Silicon Valley is a 1999 American biographical drama television film directed by Martyn
Burke and starring Noah Wyle as Steve Jobs and Anthony Michael Hall as Bill Gates.
Spanning the years 1971–1997 and based on Paul Freiberger and Michael Swaine's 1984 book Fire in the Valley: The Making of the Personal Computer, it
explores the impact that the rivalry between Jobs (Apple Computer) and Gates (Microsoft) had on the development of the personal computer.
The film premiered on TNT on June 20, 1999.
The film explores themes of computer, based on novel or
book, 1970s, biography, based on true story.
The tone is emotional.